http://www.support-intelligence.com/terms/

1. General
These Terms of Use and Privacy Policy ("Terms of Use") set forth herein apply to the www.trustfactor.com and www.support-intelligence.com web sites and related sites collectively which is owned, operated, licensed or controlled by Support Intelligence, LLC. ("Support Intelligence", "We") (collectively the "Web Site").
Please read these terms of use carefully before using the web site. By using the web site you agree to these terms of use.
IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THESE TERMS OF USE, PLEASE DO NOT USE THE WEB SITE.
We reserve the right, at our discretion, to change, modify, add, or remove portions of these Terms of Use at any time. Please check these Terms of Use periodically for changes. Your continued use of this Web Site following the posting of changes to these Terms of Use will mean you accept those changes.
2. Restrictions on use of Content and Materials
Unless specifically otherwise noted, all content and materials of this Web Site, including, but not limited to, the overall design, company logos, white-papers, pdf.s, displays, text, images, illustrations, designs, icons, photographs, forms, video clips, audio, flash and Macromedia movies, are proprietary to Support Intelligence and are protected by copyrights laws, trademarks laws and/or other intellectual property laws. No material or content from this Web Site may be copied, reproduced, republished, uploaded, posted, transmitted, or distributed in any way without express written permission from Support Intelligence.
Modification of the materials or use of the materials for any other purpose is a violation of Support Intelligence.s copyright and other proprietary rights. For purposes of these Terms of Use, the use of any such material on any other web site is prohibited. ThreatAdvisor., HackMap., AmIHacked., SecureMonitor., REACT., TRUSTFACTOR.and any other trademark or logo identifying Support Intelligence.s products are trademarks of Support Intelligence, LLC.
You may not robotically or otherwise automatically harvest information from the web site.
3. Restrictions on use of Information Regarding Third Parties
Unless otherwise noted, all information gathered on this website regarding third parties, including but not limited to private and public institutions and individuals both domestic and abroad, may not be used market to, sell to, defame, slander, insult, harm, harass, bother, or molest such entities in any way. Furthermore, this content or information shall not be used to contact third parties via any medium including but not limited to the internet and telephone for the purpose of abusing, mapping, probing, or investigating their networks, systems, servers, websites, or other electronic services via any method including but not limited to open proxies, mail system vulnerabilities, firewall vulnerabilities, botnets, or other exploits.
UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS TO ANY COMPUTER SYSTEM IS A SERIOUS CRIME AND SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE WILL FULLY COOPERATE WITH ANY LAW ENFORCEMENT AGENCY IN ANY INVESTIGATION OF ILLEGAL ACCESS.
4. Privacy Policy
Support Intelligence may gather anonymous information, which may be used by Support Intelligence or shared with third parties. This information does not necessarily personally identify you but may be helpful for improving the services we offer. Generally this information is collected via web logs and may entail the use of cookies, flash objects, IP addresses, referring pages, or other methods used to identify a computer. Support Intelligence may use the anonymous information to perform statistical analysis of user behavior in order to measure the success of various areas of our Web site, and offer specific security related information back to the user.
Personally identifiable information may also be collected about you when you use the Support Intelligence website including but not limited to voluntarily entering it into any part of the website provided by Support Intelligence. Such personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to your name, contact information, such as home or business address, zip-code, email address, user name, password of choice, credit card information, and telephone number. Support Intelligence will not use such user entered personally identifiable information other then for the purpose you have voluntarily posted it on our Web site. Upon your written request,
Support Intelligence will (a) remove information personally identifying you from our database; (b) correct personal information that you state is erroneous; (c) permit you to discontinue further email contact, while still allowing access to the site. To request a correction or cancellation, contact us through the following address support
at
support-intelligence.com
Support Intelligence takes technical, administrative and physical steps to protect against preventable risks to privacy such as unauthorized access to personally identifiable information. Support Intelligence employees or agents treat personal information as confidential and are forbidden from disclosing or handling it in unauthorized ways that jeopardize its security.
5. Disclaimer
Support Intelligence does not warrant the accuracy, wholeness or timeliness of any of the data or other information made available on the web site. The content is provided .as is. without warranty or guarantee of any kind, express or implied, including, but not limited to, implied warranties of merchantability, fitness for a particular purpose, title or non-infringement.
Support Intelligence does not warrant that the content presented on the web site will be uninterrupted or error free, or that the website are free from viruses, malware, or other harmful content.
Support Intelligence does not warrant or make any representations regarding the use or the results of the use of the materials or content on the web site in terms of its accuracy, correctness, reliability, or otherwise. You are responsible for taking all precautions you believe necessary to protect you against any claim, damage, loss, or potential harm that may arise by virtue of your use of the web site.
6. Limitation of Liability
IN NO EVENT WHATSOEVER WILL SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE OR ITS AFFILIATES BE RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE TO ANY PARTY FOR ANY DIRECT, COMPENSATORY, INDIRECT, INCIDENTAL, CONSEQUENTIAL (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS AND LOST BUSINESS OPPORTUNITIES), SPECIAL, EXEMPLARY, OR PUNITIVE DAMAGES THAT RESULT FROM OR RELATE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER TO (1) YOUR USE OF THE WEB SITE, OR RELIANCE ON THE CONTENT, OR (2) ERRORS, INACCURACIES, OMISSIONS, DEFECTS, UNTIMELINESS, SECURITY BREACHES, OR ANY OTHER FAILURE TO PERFORM BY SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE, (3) OTHERS USE OF THE WEBSITE AS IT PERTAINS TO INFORMATION REGARDING YOUR BUSINESS, ORGANIZATION, OR PERSON. THE FOREGOING EXCLUSION SHALL APPLY REGARDLESS OF WHETHER SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
IF, NOTWITHSTANDING THE OTHER TERMS OF THIS AGREEMENT, SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE SHOULD HAVE ANY LIABILITY TO YOU OR ANY THIRD PARTY FOR ANY LOSS, HARM OR DAMAGE, YOU AND SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE AGREE THAT SUCH LIABILITY SHALL UNDER NO CIRCUMSTANCES EXCEED THE GREATER OF ANY AMOUNTS PAID BY YOU DIRECTLY TO SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE OR US$1.00. YOU AND SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE AGREE THAT THE FOREGOING LIMITATION OF LIABILITY IS AN AGREED ALLOCATION OF RISK BETWEEN YOU AND SUPPORT INTELLIGENCE.
7. No Endorsement
Any reference made by this Web Site to any specific commercial product, process, service, or provider of such product, process or service, other than of Support Intelligence by trademark, hyperlink, trade name , or otherwise, does not constitute or imply an endorsement, recommendation or favoring by Support Intelligence. Content on this Web Site may be provided by third parties and users. Any opinions, advice, statements, services, offers or other information expressed or made available by third parties, including information providers, users or others, are those of the respective author(s) or distributor(s) and do not necessarily state or reflect those of Support Intelligence.
This Web Site contains links to outside services and resources over which Support Intelligence has no control concerning their availability, safety, and content. It is your responsibility to exercise due caution when visiting these sites and to take all necessary precautions to protect yourself from potential hazards contained therein.
8. Right to Terminate, Deny or Limit Access
Support Intelligence reserves the right to limit or revoke your access to this Web Site in its sole discretion, at any time, and for any reason, including, but not limited to any violation of these Terms of Use or in the event of web site corruption or other technical difficulties.
9. Termination
These Terms of Use are effective until terminated by either party or modified by Support Intelligence. You may terminate these Terms of Use at any time by destroying all materials obtained from this Web Site and all related documentation and all copies thereof, whether made under these Terms of Use or otherwise. These Terms of Use will terminate immediately without notice from Support Intelligence if in Support Intelligence.s sole discretion you fail to comply with any term or provision of these Terms of Use. Upon termination, you must destroy all materials obtained from this Web Site and all copies thereof, whether made under the terms of these Terms of Use or otherwise.
10. Governing Law and Miscellaneous
These terms shall be governed by and construed exclusively in accordance with the laws of the state of California. You agree that any action at law or in equity arising out of or relating to these terms shall be filed only in a court of competent jurisdiction within the state of California and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action. If any provision of these terms shall be unlawful, void, or for any reason unenforceable, then that provision shall be deemed severable from these terms and shall not affect the validity and enforceability of any remaining provisions.
This is the entire agreement between us relating to the subject matter herein and shall not be modified except as provided herein. We may assign this Agreement, in whole or in part, in our sole discretion. You may not assign your rights under this Agreement without our prior written permission. Any attempt by you to assign your rights under this Agreement without our permission shall be void. The waiver by us of a breach of any provision of this Agreement shall not operate or be construed as a waiver of any other or a subsequent breach of the same or a different kind.
Sign Up  |
About Us   |
Terms of Use  |
Privacy  |
Contact
© Copyright 2006-2012 Support Intelligence, Inc. • All rights reserved
